http://www.discountcell.com/privacy.htm

About Us
This is a privacy policy for Discountcell.com.
Our homepage on the Web is located at
http://www.discountcell.com.
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.
You may contact us by mail at the following address:
You may contact us by e-mail at
Info@discountcell.com.
You may call us at 1-800-422-1814.
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor
information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: • To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)• To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)• To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)• To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. • To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing
will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter you may be sent occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit card
information) will not be kept on file for more than 30 days.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally
identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist
us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long
as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also
release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with
the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property,
or safety. Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.discountcell.com/legal.htm.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.discountcell.com350 West 500 SouthProvo, UT 84601United Statesinfo@discountcell.com801-235-9809
Compact Policy Summary
The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is:
CP="IDC CURa ADMa AIa OUR DELa BUS UNI PUR COM NAV STA"
The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.
FieldMeaning
CP=
This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.
IDC
Access is available to contact information.
CURa
The data is used for completion of the current activity.
ADMa
The data is used for site administration.
DEVa
The data is used for research and development.
TAIa
The data is used for tailoring the site.
CONa
The data is used for contacting the user.
OUR
The data is given to ourselves and our agents.
DELa
The data is given to delivery services.
BUS
Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.
IND
The data will be kept indefinitely.
PHY
Physical contact information is collected.
ONL
Online contact information is collected.
UNI
Unique identifiers are collected.
PUR
Purchase information is collected.
COM
Computer information is collected.
NAV
Navigation and clickstream data is collected.
DEM
Demographic and socioeconomic data is collected.
STA
State-management data is collected
The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes.
For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment.
We keep your device running with only authentic, top quality cell phone accessories.  Buy with confidence knowing every item we offer is covered by our satisfaction guarantee and the manufacturers warranty.
Apple Accessories  |
Audiovox Accessories
|  Blackberry Accessories  |
Boost Mobile Accessories  |
HTC Accessories
|  Kyocera Accessories  |
LG Accessories
|  Motorola Accessories  |
*$.99 cent shipping (free over $50) only applies to orders shipping within the
Continental US.
Discountcell is a certified woman owned
company through the WBENC.
For questions or
comments please contact Info@DiscountCell.com.
Copyright 1997-2013 Discountcell all Rights Reserved.
Discountcell is a trademark of Discountcell Inc.
350 West 500 South, Provo UT 84601
